[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "It's a complete scam so you've got to stop this, okay?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "complete", "scam", "so", "you", "'ve", "got", "to", "stop", "this", ",", "okay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "I'm running out of time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "running", "out", "of", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brokaw"]}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What do you make of the way that he had responded to this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "way", "that", "he", "had", "responded", "to", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "It's typical Brokaw, I mean, I think there's so many of us -- I'll put myself on the first of the list, people who are grateful to Tom.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "typical", "Brokaw", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "so", "many", "of", "us", "--", "I", "'ll", "put", "myself", "on", "the", "first", "of", "the", "list", ",", "people", "who", "are", "grateful", "to", "Tom", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "And Deborah, for people who don't know Tom as well as you do, what kind of man is he?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Deborah", ",", "for", "people", "who", "do", "n't", "know", "Tom", "as", "well", "as", "you", "do", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "man", "is", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Oh God, he is the best.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "God", ",", "he", "is", "the", "best", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Deborah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "What did you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "I was always surprised that liberals are being surprised.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "always", "surprised", "that", "liberals", "are", "being", "surprised", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Is it a clever tactic?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "clever", "tactic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Oh absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Could it not backfire for Rand Paul?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "it", "not", "backfire", "for", "Rand", "Paul", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rand Paul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "What are we talking about here tonight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "we", "talking", "about", "here", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "And tell me this.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "tell", "me", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "How do the right deal with the inarguable fact that abortion levels are falling in America and the primary reason for this is increased awareness in use of contraception?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "the", "right", "deal", "with", "the", "inarguable", "fact", "that", "abortion", "levels", "are", "falling", "in", "America", "and", "the", "primary", "reason", "for", "this", "is", "increased", "awareness", "in", "use", "of", "contraception", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "I don't think that's true.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "How do you on the right handle that situation?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "on", "the", "right", "handle", "that", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I'm going to explain why this is not true now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "explain", "why", "this", "is", "not", "true", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Do you think it's good that more American women are using contraceptive?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "good", "that", "more", "American", "women", "are", "using", "contraceptive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJR", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "There is proof.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "proof", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Do you think it's good?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "There is proof that with the greater availability of contraception and the greater availability of abortion, there will be more illegitimacy.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "proof", "that", "with", "the", "greater", "availability", "of", "contraception", "and", "the", "greater", "availability", "of", "abortion", ",", "there", "will", "be", "more", "illegitimacy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Are you against then more American women using contraceptions in a responsible manner?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "against", "then", "more", "American", "women", "using", "contraceptions", "in", "a", "responsible", "manner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "I don't really care.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "really", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "You don't care?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "care", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I mean, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "From the single biggest health issues women in the world, why wouldn't you care?", "question_tokens": ["From", "the", "single", "biggest", "health", "issues", "women", "in", "the", "world", ",", "why", "would", "n't", "you", "care", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Because I'm fascinated with the debt ceiling.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "'m", "fascinated", "with", "the", "debt", "ceiling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "NN", ":", ":", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Well now, I'm putting you on the spot, are you in favor of it or not?", "question_tokens": ["Well", "now", ",", "I", "'m", "putting", "you", "on", "the", "spot", ",", "are", "you", "in", "favor", "of", "it", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "I'm opposed to promise you (ph) (inaudible) but you don't clarify that, so...", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "opposed", "to", "promise", "you", "(", "ph", ")", "(", "inaudible", ")", "but", "you", "do", "n't", "clarify", "that", ",", "so", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Isn't a good thing for America that more women are using contraception in a responsible way?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "a", "good", "thing", "for", "America", "that", "more", "women", "are", "using", "contraception", "in", "a", "responsible", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "It's not that responsible.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "that", "responsible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "I don't think what?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Any fall is a good thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Any", "fall", "is", "a", "good", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Fall?", "question_tokens": ["Fall", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "In the number of abortions.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "the", "number", "of", "abortions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Why did you have us?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "have", "us", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Because I like this girl and your mother is a catholic.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "like", "this", "girl", "and", "your", "mother", "is", "a", "catholic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "So, you and mom never actually talked about whether you want kids or not?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "and", "mom", "never", "actually", "talked", "about", "whether", "you", "want", "kids", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Oh, I figured out if we kept on scrum (ph), we'd end up with a couple of you.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "figured", "out", "if", "we", "kept", "on", "scrum", "(", "ph", ")", ",", "we", "'d", "end", "up", "with", "a", "couple", "of", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alexander Payne"]}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 359, "question": "How do you feel, I mean, what a moment for you after 80 movies to finally get nominee for a lead role?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "what", "a", "moment", "for", "you", "after", "80", "movies", "to", "finally", "get", "nominee", "for", "a", "lead", "role", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, the biggest when I've had in this whole process is that Alexander Payne invited me to come on down...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "biggest", "when", "I", "'ve", "had", "in", "this", "whole", "process", "is", "that", "Alexander", "Payne", "invited", "me", "to", "come", "on", "down", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "heard", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Well, he is a prince as far as I'm concerned.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "is", "a", "prince", "as", "far", "as", "I", "'m", "concerned", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", ":", "JJ", "NN"], "qSentId": 387, "question": "He has that stoppable (ph) authority which is good in a ray (ph) I think isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["He", "has", "that", "stoppable", "(", "ph", ")", "authority", "which", "is", "good", "in", "a", "ray", "(", "ph", ")", "I", "think", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Well, the best I ever saw had done, and you know, he wasn't really a newscaster when I was young, was (inaudible)", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "best", "I", "ever", "saw", "had", "done", ",", "and", "you", "know", ",", "he", "was", "n't", "really", "a", "newscaster", "when", "I", "was", "young", ",", "was", "(", "inaudible", ")"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom Brokaw"]}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "I'm sorry?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sorry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "No surprise to you that Tom Brokaw has carried a on working despite having been diagnosed.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "surprise", "to", "you", "that", "Tom", "Brokaw", "has", "carried", "a", "on", "working", "despite", "having", "been", "diagnosed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "That's why (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "why", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "He's just, you know, every now and then you're around across (inaudible) one.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "just", ",", "you", "know", ",", "every", "now", "and", "then", "you", "'re", "around", "across", "(", "inaudible", ")", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Did you know her at all?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "her", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "And you to a daughter that became actor as well?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "to", "a", "daughter", "that", "became", "actor", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr.", "Sean O'Casey"]}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "You also, I think in your early acting career you've got that (inaudible) and sometimes you weren't even allowed out to do a final curtain call for the audience because anyone who kill (inaudible) the mystery of you still dead on stage, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "also", ",", "I", "think", "in", "your", "early", "acting", "career", "you", "'ve", "got", "that", "(", "inaudible", ")", "and", "sometimes", "you", "were", "n't", "even", "allowed", "out", "to", "do", "a", "final", "curtain", "call", "for", "the", "audience", "because", "anyone", "who", "kill", "(", "inaudible", ")", "the", "mystery", "of", "you", "still", "dead", "on", "stage", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "-NONE-", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "The first play I was ever in was directed Mr. (inaudible) and it was called The Shadow of a Gunman it was on Sean O'Casey on Broadway and the first time the act of studio ever did a play on Broadway.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "first", "play", "I", "was", "ever", "in", "was", "directed", "Mr.", "(", "inaudible", ")", "and", "it", "was", "called", "The", "Shadow", "of", "a", "Gunman", "it", "was", "on", "Sean", "O'Casey", "on", "Broadway", "and", "the", "first", "time", "the", "act", "of", "studio", "ever", "did", "a", "play", "on", "Broadway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "When, you know, you didn't get the curtain call then and now you're going to win an Oscar, I mean a good moment, right?", "question_tokens": ["When", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "did", "n't", "get", "the", "curtain", "call", "then", "and", "now", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "win", "an", "Oscar", ",", "I", "mean", "a", "good", "moment", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Fabulous.", "answer_tokens": ["Fabulous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["morning"]}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "IN", "CD", "CC", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Is it true, John Wayne said to you, they're going to hate you for this?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "true", ",", "John", "Wayne", "said", "to", "you", ",", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "hate", "you", "for", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "He said to me about four inches in the wild (inaudible) one on one and about eight in the morning.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "said", "to", "me", "about", "four", "inches", "in", "the", "wild", "(", "inaudible", ")", "one", "on", "one", "and", "about", "eight", "in", "the", "morning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Wayne"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Berkley"]}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "And did they?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "and I said -- maybe and we got in Berkley I'm a GD (ph) hero.", "answer_tokens": ["and", "I", "said", "--", "maybe", "and", "we", "got", "in", "Berkley", "I", "'m", "a", "GD", "(", "ph", ")", "hero", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Even now?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Even in England when we went there and Gatsby was shot a lot of it I mean the Gatsby we were in and we shot a lot time with it and I run everyday.", "answer_tokens": ["Even", "in", "England", "when", "we", "went", "there", "and", "Gatsby", "was", "shot", "a", "lot", "of", "it", "I", "mean", "the", "Gatsby", "we", "were", "in", "and", "we", "shot", "a", "lot", "time", "with", "it", "and", "I", "run", "everyday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "This is fame list and yet you have never had an alcohol drink or even a coffee in your life, is that true?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "fame", "list", "and", "yet", "you", "have", "never", "had", "an", "alcohol", "drink", "or", "even", "a", "coffee", "in", "your", "life", ",", "is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I've never had a cigarette, never had a cup of coffee, never had a drink, however, I did miss a decade to Vicodin.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "never", "had", "a", "cigarette", ",", "never", "had", "a", "cup", "of", "coffee", ",", "never", "had", "a", "drink", ",", "however", ",", "I", "did", "miss", "a", "decade", "to", "Vicodin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "The TV show with a doctor who was addicted to Vicodin?", "question_tokens": ["The", "TV", "show", "with", "a", "doctor", "who", "was", "addicted", "to", "Vicodin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Huge Laurie?", "question_tokens": ["Huge", "Laurie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Laurie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Why from your perspective?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "from", "your", "perspective", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "The immediacy of his response time and I have always thought one thing that I insist on and if the actors won't do it, you just find a way to get them to do it by the way you talk to them and deal with them in the scene immediately.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "immediacy", "of", "his", "response", "time", "and", "I", "have", "always", "thought", "one", "thing", "that", "I", "insist", "on", "and", "if", "the", "actors", "wo", "n't", "do", "it", ",", "you", "just", "find", "a", "way", "to", "get", "them", "to", "do", "it", "by", "the", "way", "you", "talk", "to", "them", "and", "deal", "with", "them", "in", "the", "scene", "immediately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "But weren't they a fourth division team?", "question_tokens": ["But", "were", "n't", "they", "a", "fourth", "division", "team", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "The craft of making movies, the technique?", "question_tokens": ["The", "craft", "of", "making", "movies", ",", "the", "technique", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Since she was nine years old.", "answer_tokens": ["Since", "she", "was", "nine", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "I'll watch the World Cup with you, how about that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "watch", "the", "World", "Cup", "with", "you", ",", "how", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "RP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "I'm there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "You mean, I was sitting next to Bubba Watson?", "question_tokens": ["You", "mean", ",", "I", "was", "sitting", "next", "to", "Bubba", "Watson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bubba Watson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "RP", "EX", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "So how do you feel now you know you were next to this legend?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "now", "you", "know", "you", "were", "next", "to", "this", "legend", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Well, now I feel great, you know, I got to met him so but, you know, when hearing the story and listen to you all talk back there, I mean you learn a lot about a person and you could see that he was a big sports fan.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "now", "I", "feel", "great", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "got", "to", "met", "him", "so", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "hearing", "the", "story", "and", "listen", "to", "you", "all", "talk", "back", "there", ",", "I", "mean", "you", "learn", "a", "lot", "about", "a", "person", "and", "you", "could", "see", "that", "he", "was", "a", "big", "sports", "fan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "How many laughs are you getting out of all this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "laughs", "are", "you", "getting", "out", "of", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Pretty, pretty good I think the first couple of segments were very good.", "answer_tokens": ["Pretty", ",", "pretty", "good", "I", "think", "the", "first", "couple", "of", "segments", "were", "very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "How has being the master's champion changed your life?", "question_tokens": ["How", "has", "being", "the", "master", "'s", "champion", "changed", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "It's wild, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "wild", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Does it change everything?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "change", "everything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "It changed everything, you know, when you step on the golf course now people expect you to play good.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "changed", "everything", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "you", "step", "on", "the", "golf", "course", "now", "people", "expect", "you", "to", "play", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "POS", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Any down sides to the fame that's come with it for you?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "down", "sides", "to", "the", "fame", "that", "'s", "come", "with", "it", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Yeah, everybody expects you to play good so that's means ...", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "everybody", "expects", "you", "to", "play", "good", "so", "that", "'s", "means", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "And so close to the Super Bowl Sunday at the Phoenix Waste Management Open, one of the great titles in world sport and how do you feel when you (inaudible) when someone called the waste management open?", "question_tokens": ["And", "so", "close", "to", "the", "Super", "Bowl", "Sunday", "at", "the", "Phoenix", "Waste", "Management", "Open", ",", "one", "of", "the", "great", "titles", "in", "world", "sport", "and", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "(", "inaudible", ")", "when", "someone", "called", "the", "waste", "management", "open", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Well, I feel like I have a chance if everybody else is getting wasted like that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "feel", "like", "I", "have", "a", "chance", "if", "everybody", "else", "is", "getting", "wasted", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Phoenix Waste Management Open"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Is that swing better than yours or is that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "swing", "better", "than", "yours", "or", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "I've slightly worried he's got a more natural rhythm to his swing, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "slightly", "worried", "he", "'s", "got", "a", "more", "natural", "rhythm", "to", "his", "swing", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "He looks like he can hold of a club there?", "question_tokens": ["He", "looks", "like", "he", "can", "hold", "of", "a", "club", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Yeah for, you know, just watching me on TV and stuff and I've never said anything to him he just grabs the club and swings.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "for", ",", "you", "know", ",", "just", "watching", "me", "on", "TV", "and", "stuff", "and", "I", "'ve", "never", "said", "anything", "to", "him", "he", "just", "grabs", "the", "club", "and", "swings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Scottsville"]}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "Do you ever wish you've done anything else in life or you just still love getting up and playing golf all day?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "wish", "you", "'ve", "done", "anything", "else", "in", "life", "or", "you", "just", "still", "love", "getting", "up", "and", "playing", "golf", "all", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "I loved playing golf because it's always different it always something new and I just won my club championship last week in Scottsville so, you know, I still playing in the club tournaments at home.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "loved", "playing", "golf", "because", "it", "'s", "always", "different", "it", "always", "something", "new", "and", "I", "just", "won", "my", "club", "championship", "last", "week", "in", "Scottsville", "so", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "still", "playing", "in", "the", "club", "tournaments", "at", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Are you into the Sochi stuff at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "into", "the", "Sochi", "stuff", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "I've watched a few things but it's so political.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "watched", "a", "few", "things", "but", "it", "'s", "so", "political", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sochi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140211pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "IN", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "You know, it's sad that somebody has to feel they have to come out, like just be who you are.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "sad", "that", "somebody", "has", "to", "feel", "they", "have", "to", "come", "out", ",", "like", "just", "be", "who", "you", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]